Finding Aid for the Paul Egly Papers LSC.1282
UCLA Library Special Collections
Paul Egly papers
1977-1981
UCLA Library Special Collections
Egly, Paul
LSC.1282
56.0 Linear Feet (110 boxes, 5 oversize boxes, and 1 oversize folder)
The papers related to Judge Paul Egly's tenure of office as a Los Angeles Superior court Judge in the Los Angeles school segregation case, over which he presided from late 1976 until his resignation in March, 1981.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Paul Egly, 1981.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9912179253606533
Biography
Judge Paul Egly presided over the case of Crawford, etc. et al. v. Board of Education of the City of Los Angeles.
Scope and Content
The bulk of material relates to the case of Crawford, etc. et al. v. Board of Education of the City of Los Angeles and related appeals. The case resulted in numerous Los Angeles Unified School District desegregation plans, including substantial pupil reassignment and busing. The papers are comprised of correspondence, duplicate exhibits, pleadings, studies, reports and maps.
Organization and Arrangement
Most of the packing cartons in which the papers were donated were numbered: they have been unpacked and boxed in that numbered order, with the original carton number in square brackets noted. Box descriptions in inverted commas are those which appeared on the packing cartons and the information given below has sometimes been supplemented by a rough listing (kept in the Collections File), derived from partly typed and partly handwritten notes, which were prepared by the Judge's staff at the time of the transfer of the papers. Also available from the Collections File upon request are copies of the Court receipts for exhibits, which constitute a descriptive list (Boxes 30-36).
Related Material
Helen V. Smookler papers on School Integration (Collection 1547). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections.
Monroe Edwin Price Collection about School Integration (Collection 1391). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections.
Los Angeles School Monitoring Committee (Collection 1291). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections.
School integration -- Law and legislation -- California -- Los Angeles -- Archives.; Judges -- California -- Los Angeles -- Archives.; Egly, Paul--Archives.; Los Angeles Unified School District
- 1) Plaintiffs appellate briefs, [cartons 1-2] (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4)
  - Petitioners - California Supreme Court Petition, 1980 September 5
  - Petitioners - U.S. Supreme Court Petition, 1980 September 8 (Volume 5, Volume 6)
  - Petitioners - Exhibits to California Supreme Court, 1980 September 5
  - Petitioners - DCA Appeal, 1980 December
  - Petitioners - DCA Appeal - California Supreme Court - Application for transfer to U.S. Supreme Court, 1980 August 11
  - Petitioners Exhibits to Petition Writ of Mandate California Supreme Court
  - Petitioners - DCA Response to Writ of Prohibition - Declaration of Joe Duff, 1980 September 16
  - Petitioners - Response to application for stay - U.S. Supreme Court, 1979 October
  - Petitioners - Application for Leave to file more than 60 page DCA, 1980 December 15
  - Petitioners - DCA appeal from Order of Superior Court, 1981 January 3
  - Petitioners - Reply Brief to Respondent Appeal of July 7 Order, 1980 December 15
  - Petitioners - Appendix to Appellants Brief DCA, 1980 December 15
  - Petitioners - Exhibits to Petition Writ of Mandate California Supreme Court, 1980 September
  - Petitioners - Declaration for more than 50 pages DCA, 1980 November 13
  - Petitioners - Opening Brief on Appeal from July 7 order DCA, 1980 November 12
  - Petitioners - California Supreme Court Appeal from Order, 1981 September 25
  - Petitioners - Petition for Writ of Mandate California Supreme Court, 1980 September 15
  - Petitioners - DCA, Brief of Respondents Proposition L, 1980 November 26
  - Petitioners - DCA Application for 50 pages Brief Proposition L, 1980 November 26
  - Petitioners - DCA, Motion to Modify Orders of October for Records, 1980 October 10
  - Petitioners - Reply to Relief from Best DCA, 1980 October 8
  - Opposition to Respond Application to Augment, 1980 November 18
  - DCA, Reply to Application for Temporary Stay, 1980 August 4
  - Supreme California Court, Emergency Petition for Writ, 1980 August 11
  - DCA, Reply to Petition for Writ of Supercedeas - DCA, Response of Real parties for Writ of Mandate, 1980 September 13
- 2) Respondents appellate briefs, [carton 2] (Box 4, Box 5, Box 6)
  - Respondent - Petition for Writ of Mandate - DCA, 1980 July 24
  - Respondent - Petition for Writ of Supersedeas - DCA, 1980 July 24
  - Respondent - Exhibits to Petition for Writ of Supersedeas, DCA, 1980 July 24 (Volume I, Volume II, Volume III)
  - Respondent - DCA Appeal from Superior Court Order, Reply to Plaintiff's Brief, 1980 December 3
  - Respondent - DCA, First Appellant's Reply to Plaintiff's Brief on Appeal from July 7 Order, 1980 December
  - Respondent - DCA, first Appellant's Opening Brief on Appeal from July 7 Order, 1980 November 13
  - Respondent - DCA, Application for Order to Augment Record on Appeal, 1980 November 13
  - Respondent - Appellant's Answer to Petition for Rehearing, 1980 January 12
  - Respondent - Mailgram from G.W. Shea to Chief Justice re Egly letter to California Supreme Court, 1980 September 16
  - Respondent - Mailgram from G.W. Shea, 1980 September 17
  - Respondent - Designation of Record to Supreme Court for Appeal of July 7, 1980 August 4
  - Respondent - Designation of Record for Appeal from May 19 Order, 1980 August 4
  - Respondent - Petition for Writ of Mandate, DCA, 1980 July 25
  - Respondent - Petition for Writ of Mandate, DCA Supercedeas, 1980 July 24
  - Respondent - Ex Parte Application for Superior Court for Extentions, 1980 July 24
  - Respondent - Petition for Writ and Volumes I and II, DCA - Exhibits to Petition for Writ of Mandate, 1980 August 28
  - Respondent - DCA, Appeal from Order, 1980 December 5
  - Respondent - DCA, Brief re Proposition L, 1980 December
  - Respondent - U.S. Superior Court, 1980
  - Respondent - Application for Stay, 1980 September 8
  - Respondent - DCA, Reply to Petitioners Application, 1980 November 19
- "Correspondence and notes,. Some pleadings.", 1977-1979; [carton 3] (Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 10, Box 11, Box 12, Box 13, Box 14, Box 15, Box 16, Box 17, Box 18, Box 19, Box 20, Box 21, Box 22, Box 23)
  - A-Bi (Box 7)
    - Ablon, Paul S. (Box 7)
      - Analysis of the Crawford Opinion, 1977 March 2
    - Abstracts (Box 7)
      - Abstracts of plan and plan concepts for pupil integration--appendices to ninth report of the court referee, 1977 September 8
    - ACLU Foundation (Box 7)
      - Correspondence
    - Aldama (Box 7)
      - LAUSD - Option 1 Component Development Option
    - Amfen (Box 7)
    - Amicus Curiae (Box 7)
      - John Caughey, 1 expando folder, 1 file folder
        Scope and Contents note
        Documents filed by Caughey, correspondence
      - Requests to Intervene
      - Max Schneier, member, National Planning and Advisory Council White House Conference on Handicapped Individuals--filed brief with Court of Appeal, 1978 September 14
    - Appeals Court (Box 7)
      - Second Appellate District, Crawford v. Superior Court, Board of Education, Real Parties in Interest
    - Assembly California Legislature (Box 7)
      - Letter from Howard L. Berman, 1979 February 22
    - Attorney Fees (Box 7)
    - Attorney General (Box 7)
      - Evelle J. Younger, et.al., amicus curiae in support of Bustop
    - Attorneys in Case (Box 7)
      - List of attorneys and their phone numbers and addresses
    - Aubry, Larry (Box 7)
      - Correspondence re Crawford case, 1977 December 12
    - BEST (Better Education for Students Today) (Box 7)
      - Memorandum; Motions; Correspondence
  - Bi-Ci (Box 8)
    - Bilingual-Bicultural (Box 8)
      - Correspondence
    - Bills (Box 8)
      - Senate and Assembly Bills
    - Black Education Commission (Box 8)
    - Black Leadership Coalition (Box 8)
    - Board of Education (Box 8)
      - Correspondence, articles, etc.
    - Board of Supervisors (Box 7)
      - Correspondence re School Integration case
    - Brown Decision (Box 8)
      - Prejudice and Pride After 25 Years, Report from the National Academy of Education, Stephen K. Bailey, Rapporteur
    - Brown v. Board of Education of Topeka, Shawnee County, Kansas (Box 8)
    - Bustop (Box 8)
    - Campbell, Senator (Box 8)
      General note
      (See Foundation for Constitutional Education)
    - Choice (Box 8)
      Prepared by Robert A. Smith.
    - Chronology of L.A. School Case
    - Citations (Box 8)
    - City Council of the City of Los Angeles (Box 8)
    - City Councils (Box 8)
      - Resolutions opposing Metropolitan Plan
  - Ci-Enr., [carton 5] (Box 9)
    - Clerk (Box 9)
      - Law Clerk for Crawford Case
    - Commission on Human Relations (Box 9)
    - Correspondence re Crawford v. Board (Box 9)
    - Council for Peace and Equality in Education (Box 9)
      - Barbara Rasmussen, Arthur Gardner
    - Counsel (Box 9)
      - Correspondence
    - Department of Education (Box 9)
      - California, School Finance Equalization Project
    - Depositions Taken Since Return of Plan I, from Joseph Duff, NAACP (Box 9)
    - Disqualification (Box 9)
      (See Egly, Judge)
    - Drafts, rough outlines, Judge Egly (Box 9)
    - Education Code Section 422 43.6 (Box 9)
      - County Counsel letter 2/17/78 to L.A. Unified School with Judge Egly's minute order of 2/778 attached
    - Egly, Judge (Box 9)
      - Answer to Statement of Disqualification filed by Thomas F. Bartman
    - El Centro School District (Box 9)
      - (Flores v. El Centro)
  - Env.-Ham (Box 10)
    - Environment Report, 1973 October 18 1974 October 14 1975 October 16 1976 October 28 (Box 10)
    - Environment Impact Report (Box 10)
      - Citizens League Defense Alliance
    - EPU (Educational Planning Units) (Box 10)
    - Foundation for Constitutional Education, signed by Senator Campbell (Box 10)
    - Hain, Elwood (Box 10)
      - University of San Diego School of Law, Correspondence, etc.
    - Halverson, Jerry F., Associate Superintendent, Los Angeles Unified School District (Box 10)
      - Correspondence, etc., Business and Personnel Services
    - Hamilton-Rabinovitiz, Inc. (Box 10)
      - Correspondence, etc. Budget Amendment, 1979 August 13
  - Har-J (Box 11)
    - Harvard Educational Review (Box 11)
      - Desegregating Urban Schools, Review Techniques
    - Harvard Law School, Derrick Bell, Professor of Law (Box 11)
      - letter with articles, The Yale Law Journal, Waiting on the Promise of Brown Legal Analysis, 1970 February 12
    - Hickman, Melvin, G. (Box 11)
      - Narrative Summary of the Credo Design, 1977 October 14
    - History of Integration (Box 11)
      - The Happenings at the L.A. Board of Education
    - Individual Guided Education at Lenay Road School from Barbara Rolston (Box 11)
    - Integration Incentive Act (Box 11)
      - Model by John E. Coons and Stephan Sugarman Childhood and Government Project, Earl Warren Legal Institute, University of California, Berkeley, 1977 April
    - Integration Project (Box 11)
    - Intervenors, Dreebin (Box 11)
    - Intervenors, Loveland (Box 11)
      - CACSI, Correspondence, etc.
    - Invitations, Speeches, Interviews, Judge Egly (Box 11)
    - Isolated Minorities (Box 11)
      - Identification of, from desegregation Task Force Office of L.A. Superintendent of Schools, E. Maylon Drake
    - Jenkins, Dr. Robert E., County Superintendent of Schools, San Francisco Unified School District (Box 11)
      - Educational Equality/Quality Report No. 3, letter to him, 1978 November 2
    - Johnston, William J., Superintendent of Schools, LAUSD (Box 11)
      - Correspondence, etc.
    - Justice, U.S. Department of (Box 11)
      - Community Relations Service, Western Region
  - K - Letters (anti-busing), 1979; [carton 6] (Box 12)
    - Kentucky Case (Box 12)
    - LAU Plan (Box 12)
    - League of Women Voters (Box 12)
      - Correspondence
    - Letters Addressed To Others, with copy to Judge Egly (Box 12)
    - Letters, Anti-busing, Answered, 1977 (Box 12)
  - Letters (pro-busing), 1977 (Box 13)
  - Letters answered, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Letters answered, 1979 April-December (Box 14)
  - Letters received while in Los Angeles (not answered) (Box 14)
    - Letters from persons associated with organizations, schools, etc. (Box 14)
  - Letters unanswered (Box 15)
    - Letters not answered from General Magnifico, and others (Box 15)
    - Letters not answered from the Public (No. 1, 2, 3) (Box 15)
  - Letters from Ralph Reid - Loz, [carton 7] (Box 16)
    - Letters from Reid (Ralph F. Reid, 1201 West Valencia Drive, Space #25 Fullerton, CA 92633) (Box 16)
    - Letters from H.E. Lozoya (Anti-busing letters) (Box 16)
    - Letters Urging Integration (Box 16)
      - Form letter, 1979 May 29
    - Lofton, Leon (Box 16)
      - Correspondence re Lofton v. LAUSD
    - Lopez-Lee, David (Box 16)
      - Position and Statement Policy, Chicano Concern
    - Los Angeles Times (Box 16)
      - William Trombley, etc.
    - Los Angeles Unified School District (Box 16)
      - Chronology of Procedures, etc.
      - General Outline of Pupil Integration, correspondence
      - Integration Progress Report,; Integration Concern Area E., miscellaneous other, 1977 July 21 1977 December 9
      - Response to Item 4 of minute order of Desegregation Simulation, 1977 July 5
    - Loveland and Keipp (Box 16)
      (See Intervenors)
  - M - Miscellaneous (Box 17)
    - Magnet Schools (Box 17)
    - Maps (Box 17)
    - Massachusetts Department of Education (Box 17)
      - Critical Issues in Magnet Schools, a state prospective, furnished through Helene Smookler
    - Mayor's City Education Advisory Committee (Box 17)
    - Mercer, Jane Report (Box 17)
    - Metropolitan Plan (Box 17)
      - Bustops's opposition, 1979 June 6
      - Correspondence relating to
    - Mexican-American (Box 17)
      - The American Elementary School versus the Values and needs of Mexican-American Boys. University of California at Irvine, 1971 May. by Ethel M. Hepner.
    - Minute Orders, (Incomplete)
    - Miscellaneous and Sundry Items re School Integration Case (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Reports - Orange County, [carton 8] (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous reports, surveys and plans (Box 18)
    - Monitoring Committee (Box 18)
      - Charge to, Reports, etc.
    - Nelson, Dorothy (Box 18)
      - Correspondence re, L.A. School case
    - Newspaper Articles, Publications (Box 18)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 18)
      - School Desegregation in other areas, various
      - Duplicates in Scrapbooks
    - Notes by Judge Egly re School Case (Box 18)
    - Notice To Whom It May Concern By United Citizens for Constitutional Law, Blue form (Box 18)
    - Ohio School Citizens Council (Box 18)
    - Orange County (Box 18)
      - (North Education Forum and Whittier Area Education Study Council - Judge Egly Speech), 1979 February 8
  - Order-Q (Box 19)
    - Pacoima Junior High School (Box 19)
      - Pairs and Clusters
    - Palo Alto (Box 19)
      - (Tinsley v. Palo Alto Unified School District)
        See Tinsley v. Palo Alto.
    - Plan Activity 1 thru 14 (Box 19)
      - Sources of Commitments and Examples of Related Plans
    - Plans Submitted by Private Parties (Box 19)
    - Pretrial Order, 1977 November 17 (Box 19)
      - List of issues to be addresses, 1977 November 17
      - Questions pursuant to the mandate of this court and a subsequent minute order, 1977 July 5
      - Amendment to Pretrial Order
    - Profiles of Schools Performance, 1975-1976 (Box 19)
      - L.A. County, CA, Assessment Program, California State Department of Education
    - PWT (Permits with Transportation) (Box 19)
    - Questions Propounded to The Respondent by The Court, 1977 November 21 (Box 19)
      - Letter to Mr. Shea
      - Answers of Respondents to 22 Questions asked by Judge Egly filed, 1977 November 29
      - Exhibits to Respondent's Answers
      - Letter to Mr. Shea by Herb Cox, 1977 December 8
      - Percentage by other White and Combined Minority Students by School, etc.
  - R-Sch. (Box 20)
    - Recall of Judge Egly (Box 20)
      - Correspondence, etc.
    - RIMS (Racially Isolated Minority Schools) (Box 20)
      - RIMS Components
    - San Diego State University (Box 20)
      - Major Student Ethnic Minority Group Concentrations in the California Public Schools Research Report No. 1
    - San Diego Unified School District, Judge Louis M. Welch
      - Correspondence to Justice Wright
    - Save Our Schools versus Superior Court of the State of California, 1978 December (Box 20)
      - (Memorandum of Points and Authorities in Opposition for Petition of Writ of Mandate) sent by Judge Hogoboom for possible hearing by Judge Egly
  - Sch-Sm, [carton 9] (Box 21)
    - Schools (Box 21)
      - Brentwood Unified Science Center, re Monitoring Committee
      - Correspondence re Magnets, Metropolitan Plan, Clusters, etc.
    - Segregated Minority Junior High Schools (Box 21)
    - Segregated Minority Not in EPU's (Box 21)
    - Segregated Minority Senior High Schools (Box 21)
    - Serna and Wilson (Box 21)
      - Appellate Department's Opinion and Judgment
    - Serrano v. Priest (Box 21)
    - Sheriff's Department (Box 21)
      - (Operation Plan Security of Judge Egly)
    - Simulations (Box 21)
    - SLC/WEST (Box 21)
      - (Southern Leadership Conference, Marnesba T. Tackett, Executive Director)
  - St.-Whi (Box 22)
    - State Board of Education Regulations (Box 22)
      - Decisions of the California Supreme Court in the cases of Crawford v. LAUSD and San Bernardino Unified School District
    - Statistics (Box 22)
    - Supreme Court of the State of California (Box 22)
      - Order Denying Alternative Writ, signed by Rose Bird, Chief Justice
    - Supreme Court of the United States (Box 22)
      - Bustop's Application for Stay, denied by Justice Rehnquist, 1978 September 8
      - Bustop's Application for Stay, denied by Justice Powell, 1978 September 11
    - Telegrams (Box 22)
      - School Integration Case
    - Tinsley v. The State of California (Box 22)
      - Correspondence from Bert Glenn Memorandum concerning Joinder, 1978 December 5
    - Trials (Box 22)
      - Motions for Continuances, Supporting Declaration of David T. Peterson
    - UCLA (Box 22)
      - Meeting held, 1978 March 11
    - UCLA School of Law (Box 22)
      - Bert Glenn, Multi-District Desegregation
    - United Teacher/Los Angeles (UTLA) (Box 22)
      - Leave to Intervene, 1979 July 31
    - U.S. Commission on Civil Rights (Box 22)
      - School Desegregation
    - University of California (Box 22)
      - Professor W. James Popham, Detroit High School Proficiency Program Criteria--Reference Measurement
    - Voluntary Plans (Box 22)
  - 1) Wi-Z (Box 23)
    - Weintraub, Roberta, President Board of Education, City of Los Angeles (Box 23)
    - White, Gregory L. and Harold B. Girard (Box 23)
      - Conflict, Decision and Attention to Choice Alternatives, University of California
    - Wilshire Complex (Box 23)
      - Correspondence
    - Witnesses (Box 23)
    - Yale Law Journal (Box 23)
      - De Facto, De Jure Distinction
    - Yeazell, Stephen C. (Box 23)
      - Intervention and the Idea of Litigation
      - A Commentary on the Los Angeles School Case
  - 2) Bustop pleadings, 1977 - 1978 June 23; [carton 10] (Box 23)
    - Memorandum, 1977 September 15; File No. 1 (Box 23)
      re Circumstances under which State of California and its Political Subdivisions may become necessary and/or indispensable parties to case.
    - Pretrial Memorandum, 1977 November 14; File No. 2 (Box 23)
      Concerning Remaining Issues and Order of Proceedings
    - First Set of Interrogatories Propounded to Board of Education, 1977 November 29; File No. 3 (Box 23)
    - Statement of Disqualification of Judge; Memorandum of Points and Authorities, 1977 December 30; File No. 4 (Box 23)
    - Notice of Motion and Motion for Leave to File Objections to the Plan files 1977 October 3, 1978 January 23; File No. 5 (Box 23)
    - Notice of Motion for Mistrial, 1978 January 23; File No. 5 (Box 23)
    - Notice of Ruling, 1978 January 30; File No. 5 (Box 23)
    - Brief, 1978 February 22; File No. 5 (Box 23)
      re Selection and use of Experts
    - Notice of Motion for Orders, 1978 May 2; File No. 6 (Box 23)
      1. Disqualifying Experts Crain, Pettigrew and Orfield
      2. Limiting Communications with Experts, etc.
    - Notice of Motion for an Order Clarifying the Court's minute Order of 1978 February 7, 1978 April 18; File No. 7 (Box 23)
    - Memorandum of Points and Authorities in Support of Motion to Stay Implementation of Plan 2, 1978 June 23; File No. 8 (Box 23)
      Volumes I and II, Exhibits to Memorandum
  - Bustop pleadings, 1978 July 17 - 1979 July 10 (Box 24)
    - Bustop's Reply Memorandum, 1978 July 17; File No. 8a (Box 24)
      (dismissal of case, stay of plan, excessive bus rides)
    - Bustop's Motion for Stay of Proceedings, 1978 August 3; File No. 8a (Box 24)
      Bustop's Motion for Stay of Proceedings
    - Notice of Appeal to Second District Court from Order of Stay of Proceedings, 1978 August 4; File No. 8a (Box 24)
    - Bustop's Motion for Order Directing Referee Price to deliver copies of Farley Report, 1978 July 17; File No. 9 (Box 24)
    - Bustop's Fourteenth Amendment Memorandum, 1978 July 26; File No. 10 (Box 24)
    - Petitioner's Reply to Bustop's Fourteenth Amendment, 1978 August 2; File No. 10 (Box 24)
    - Dreebin's Reply Memorandum to Bustop's Fourteenth Amendment, 1978 August 3; File No. 10 (Box 24)
    - Exhibits to Bustop's Second Supplemental Memorandum, 1978 August 4; File No. 11 (Box 24)
      re Motion to Declare Respondent Recalcitrant - Exhibits A-L
    - Other Exhibits, File No. 11 (Box 24)
    - Supplemental Memo to declare respondent recalcitrant, 1978 December 7; File No. 11 (Box 24)
    - Bustop's Opposition to Integration Project's Motion to declare respondent recalcitrant, 1979 October 9; File No. 11 (Box 24)
    - Bustop's Requests for Factual Information generated by the respondent, 1979 April 2; File No. 12 (Box 24)
      Filed pursuant to the court's minute order of 1979 March 26
    - Ninth Grade Classes, 1979 July 10; File No. 13 (Box 24)
  - 1) Bustop pleadings: miscellaneous, motions re motion to declare respondent recalcitrant, 1980 (Box 25)
    - Bustop's Notice of Continuance of Deposition of Max Barney, 1978 July 6; File No. 14 (Box 25)
    - Bustop's Amended Notice of Continuance of Depo of Richard Caldwell, 1978 July 10; File No. 14 (Box 25)
    - Bustop's Amended Notice of Taking Depo of Jordan, Barnie, Caldwell, Halverson, Johnston, File No. 14 (Box 25)
    - Notice of Termination of Association of Carol Lavender with Bustop, File No. 14 (Box 25)
    - Notice of Association of Cliff Fridkis as counsel, File No. 14 (Box 25)
    - Bustop's Substitution of Thomas F. Bartman in place of Paul, Hastings, etc., File No. 14 (Box 25)
    - Bustop's Notice Designating papers and Records for incorporation in record on appeal and notice to prepare reporter's transcript, File No. 14 (Box 25)
    - Order extending time to file, File No. 14 (Box 25)
    - Notice to prepare reporter's and clerk's transcripts, File No. 14 (Box 25)
    - Bustop's Memo, 1979 March 21; File No. 14 (Box 25)
      re Motion for Order to Show Cause
    - Recalcitrance, File No. 15 (Box 25)
  - 2) John Caughey; Amicus curiae pleadings, [carton 11] (Box 25-26)
    - Caughey's Pleadings, 1978 (Box 25-26)